<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Machine Learning on InfinitynCore</title><link>/tags/machine-learning/</link><description>Recent content in Machine Learning on InfinitynCore</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 12:34:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Ultimate Free Resource List for Aspiring AI &amp; Data Science Professionals</title><link>/posts/free-ai-ml-data-science-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 12:34:24 +0530</pubDate><guid>/posts/free-ai-ml-data-science-resources/</guid><description>In our last post, we laid out the roadmap for a career in AI, ML, and Data Science. We talked about the what—the skills you need to build. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the how and the where.
One of the most incredible things about this field is the sheer volume of high-quality, free educational content available online. The barrier to entry has never been lower. To help you navigate this ocean of information, I&amp;rsquo;ve curated a list of the best free resources to take you from beginner to proficient.</description></item><item><title>Your Roadmap to a Career in AI, ML, and Data Science in 2025</title><link>/posts/aiml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:22:11 +0530</pubDate><guid>/posts/aiml/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence (AI), Machine Learning (ML), and Data Science are no longer just buzzwords; they are the engines driving the most significant technological advancements of our time. From the recommendation engine that suggests your next movie to groundbreaking medical diagnoses, these fields are reshaping our world.
For a newcomer, breaking into this domain can feel like trying to climb a mountain in the fog. The sheer volume of tools, algorithms, and concepts is daunting.</description></item></channel></rss>